LAUREL THORBURN, AuD, CCC-A

Area: Aurora, CO 80016 | Phone: 303-736-9393 | Email: codinglaurel@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/laurelthorburn

WEB DEVELOPER

Creative and proficient object-oriented web developer with extensive history of working in client facing, team-oriented roles. Fast learner who's reliable, enthusiastic, and methodical. Experience with MERN stack, CSS, semantic and accessible HTML, JavaScript, jQuery, React, NoSQL, MySql, Express, and Node.js.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Accessibility
- Bootstrap/Bulma
- CSS
- Express
- Git

- GraphQL
- Heroku
- HTML
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Jest

- MySQL/NoSQL
- NextJS
- Node
- ReactJS
- TypeScript

PROJECTS

DONUT-FORGET | https://github.com/laurelthorburn/DONUT-FORGET-TO-REVIEW

Full stack application utilizing Node.js, Sequelize, MySql, Handlebars, and Cloudinary. Site allows users to create posts with images, leave comments, and login/logout of their session to keep their data secure by using local storage and cookies.

"React Portfolio" | https://laurelthorburn.github.io/Laurel-Thorburn-Portfolio/

Created a responsive, mobile first, single page application portfolio using React.js, EmailJS, and Node. User is able to render an about page, contact page, resume, and projects of Laurel Thorburn. Weather Dashboard | https://github.com/laurelthorburn/Weather-Dashboard

Created a user-friendly weather dashboard that uses a third-party API, openweathermap.org, to fetch weather data and store results in local storage. Results are dynamically created using JavaScript and jQuery and are displayed in cards created by a CSS library, Bootstrap.

EXPERIENCE

Kaiser Permanente: Lead Clinical Audiologist

11/2019 - present

Working with pediatric and adult patients providing diagnostic and rehabilitation services, such as audiological evaluations, hearing aid consultations, and fittings.

Aurora/Cherry Creek Public Schools: Educational Audiologist

07/2017 - 10/2019

08/2021 - present

Worked with students, ages 0 to 21 years of age, and families of diverse cultures, backgrounds, languages, and disorders providing audiological evaluations and services.

EDUCATION

University Denver (DU), Denver, CO Full Stack Developer Certificate

University of Colorado (CU), Boulder, CO 08/2013 – 05/2017

Doctorate of Audiology (AuD)